[{"question": "  hello.", "answer": "  hey, it\u0092s me. i know you can\u0092t stand to be in the same room as me, so i just thought i\u0092d try and apologize over the phone. all i\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": "  hello.", "answer": " look i never should have kissed your girlfriend, but i\u0092m\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  stop callin\u0092!!", "answer": "  hey! hey! hey! this is 92.3, wxrk, k-rock for our $1,000 daily challenge.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " all right!", "answer": " what is the name of your roommate who is very, very sorry and would do anything\u009a  opening credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": "  aww, turkey! aww, giving thanks! aww!", "answer": " look everyone, it\u0092s the spirit of thanksgiving!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " so are things with you and joey any better?", "answer": " they couldn\u0092t be worse. i spent eight hours calling him last night, just trying to get him to talk to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " oh wow, eight hours? so you could probably really use one of those plug-in telephone headsets huh?", "answer": " should we all expect christmas gifts that can be stolen from your office?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " you shouldn\u0092t.", "answer": " speaking of christmas, umm since monica and i are starting a new business and have like no money, umm, this year maybe we could do secret santa, and then we each only buy one gift. and-and there\u0092s the added mystery of who gets who.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " well, i\u0092m gonna take a nap, turkey makes me sleepy.", "answer": " we haven\u0092t eaten yet!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " hey, by any chance did either of pick uh rachel for your secret santa, \u0091cause i wanna trade for her.", "answer": " i picked her! oh thank god you want her! ooh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " wow! why do you want to get rid of her so badly?", "answer": " because she exchanges every gift she ever gets, it\u0092s like impossible to get her something she likes. come on, let\u0092s trade!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh that\u0092s not true! that\u0092s not true! i got her that backpack and she loved it! i remember how much she was crying the day when that big dog ran off with it\u009a  oh, there was no big dog. all right this sucks! i already got her this briefcase, and i had r.g. put on it\u009a  her initials\u009a", "answer": " ohh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " well, maybe you could give to somebody else. ooh, like ross geller.", "answer": " op, y'know what though, it\u0092s kind\u0092ve a girlie briefcase.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " who cares? he works in a museum!", "answer": " hey, what time is it? the big game is about to start!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " you don\u0092t have to do that, ross and joey aren\u0092t here, you can watch the parade if you want.", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " what is wrong with this freezer?!  ow! ow!!", "answer": " god, what happened?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " oh my god, ice just got in my eye!", "answer": "  people are trying to sleep in here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " monica got ice in her eye, and it hurts.", "answer": " open it up, let me see.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " oh, y\u0092know what, i can\u0092t, it really kills.", "answer": " well maybe you should put some ice on it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " ooh, god it looks bad.", "answer": " honey, maybe we should take you to a doctor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " no, my eye doctor is richard! i can\u0092t go to him when i don\u0092t have a boyfriend!", "answer": " he\u0092s really picky about his patients.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " honey, you\u0092ve got to go. what\u0092s his office number?", "answer": " like i remember his office number!  speed dial 7.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": "  hi! yeah, i\u0092m calling on behalf of monica geller\u0092s eye, and is um, is richard burke in today.   he\u0092s out of town, but does she want to see the on-call doctor?", "answer": " yes!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " hey-hey, i thought she told you to follow the recipe exactly!", "answer": " okay, get out of my kitchen!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": "  all right! okay! i think i am making some progress with joey, when i went into the apartment he went straight into his bedroom but he only slammed the door once!  i mean yeah, he gave me the finger while doing it.", "answer": " all right i\u009a i gotta call my mom and ask her a left handed cooking question.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " so listen ah, i picked monica for secret santa, but i\u0092m already getting her something for chanukah, i was wondering if you wanna switch.", "answer": " oh y\u0092know what, i was already trying to trade for ah, well, you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " really?! wow! that\u0092s-that\u0092s so nice, what are you gonna get me?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know r.g., i was thinking something girlie for your office.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " yeah, well maybe phoebe will switch with me.", "answer": " oh no-no-no, you don\u0092t want to do that, then you\u0092re gonna get stuck with rachel and she exchanges every gift she ever gets.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " oh, that\u0092s not true! i\u0092ve got her lots of stuff she never took back.", "answer": " like?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " like uh, that gold necklace i got her last year.", "answer": " when was the last time you saw her wear it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " well, she wore it all christmas day, and then uh\u009a", "answer": " big dog?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " what are you doing?", "answer": " i\u0092m sending back all this stuff that chandler bought out of guilt.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " everything? even the tv?", "answer": " no! i\u0092m putting that in my room.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " listen, joey, i know what he did was wrong but don\u0092t you think you could at least hear the guy out?", "answer": " back when you and rachel were together, if chandler had kissed her, would you hear him out?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " that\u0092s a good point. so uh, how long are you gonna punish him?", "answer": " five years.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " you\u0092ve sentenced him?!", "answer": " hey! don\u0092t do the crime if you can\u0092t do the time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " joey, the guy\u0092s your best friend.", "answer": " no, was my best friend. anyway, i don\u0092t know why you\u0092re pushing for him so hard. with him out of the way as my best friend, there\u0092s a spot open.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " oh, who? me?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " wow! i\u0092m honored! and y\u0092know what i\u0092m gonna do as my first act as your best friend?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " i\u0092m gonna get you to talk to chandler.", "answer": " all right. but if you weren\u0092t my best friend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " oh my god, is it really that bad?", "answer": " i walk into a room and he won\u0092t even talk to me, he just mumbles something in italian. and i know he only knows the bad words.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": "  hey gunther, have you uh, have you seen chandler?", "answer": " i thought you were chandler. but umm, one of who is over there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " hey joe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " i\u0092ll be right with you. okay?  thanks, wendy.", "answer": " oh my god! how cute is the on-call doctor?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " dr. burke will see you know.", "answer": " oh no-no-no, not dr. burke. dr. burke is out of town. the-the on-call doctor will see me now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " hey! i\u0092m sorry! that\u0097 where are you going?", "answer": " my folks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " oh, uh, when-when are you coming back?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know. i might stay there for a few days while i look for an apartment.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " yeah, y\u0092know at first i thought we could talk about this y\u0092know, work it out, but uh, seeing you two together i don\u0092t think i\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " hey, look, what do you want me to say? do you want me to say that i\u0092ll stop seeing her?", "answer": " look, it\u0092s not about her. okay? but seeing you two together just reminds me of what you did. and i don\u0092t want to live with some one who doesn\u0092t know what it is to be a friend. so, i\u0092ll see ya.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " hey, look, i know what it is to be a friend, i just-i just screwed up!", "answer": " yeah! you did! and that\u0092s why i\u0092m leaving.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " all right look, if you\u0092re not gonna stay for me, then at least stay for them! okay, they have had a very difficult year! what with the robbery and all!", "answer": " when that guy was robbing us, and i was locked in the entertainment unit for like six hours, you know what i was doing in there all that time? i was thinking about how i let you down!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " yeah! but if would\u0092ve know what kind of friend you were gonna turn out to be, i wouldn\u0092t have worried about it so much! see you around!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " all right, wait! come on! just wait one second! there has to be something that i can do! something! if we still had that entertainment unit i would get in it for six hours and think about how i let you down.  what?", "answer": " we\u0092ve got a box.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " last time i saw you, it was the morning i left for college. and you were just standing outside the dairy queen.", "answer": " i was probably waiting for it to open.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " i gotta tell you, you look great now.", "answer": " you look great too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " you\u0092re an excellent patient!", "answer": " so how does it look?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " well, you\u0092ve got a little scratch on your cornea, your gonna have to wear a patch for a couple of days.", "answer": " like a pirate?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " if that helps you.", "answer": " umm, so how long have you been working with your dad?  come on, one of us had to mention him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " i moved back here a couple of months ago.", "answer": " oh. big family dinner tonight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " no way!", "answer": " i was gonna have thanksgiving at my girlfriend\u0092s.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": "  oh.", "answer": " but we broke up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": "  oh.", "answer": " she-she wasn\u0092t ready for a serious commitment.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  oh.  so you made her walk the plank? aye, matie?", "answer": " you\u0092re not wearing the patch yet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " he\u0092s coming here for thanksgiving!", "answer": " i know, it\u0092s sick.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " why is it sick?", "answer": " because it\u0092s richard\u0092s son! it\u0092s like inviting greek tragedy over for dinner!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " hey, come on, phoebe, you understand don\u0092t you?", "answer": " yeah, i can see where i\u0092d be your best shot but, no. i\u0092m sorry, but i think it\u0092s twisted.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": "  what\u0092s twisted?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " me going out with richard\u0092s son.", "answer": " ewwwww!! ew! ew! ew!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": "  sounds like a really bad idea to me.", "answer": " is he okay in there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " he\u0092s fine!", "answer": " hey, y'know, mon, if things wrong out between you and richard\u0092s son, you\u0092d be able to tell your kids, that you slept with their grandfather.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " so now, what exactly is the point of the box?", "answer": " chandler?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " the meaning of the box is three fold. one , it gives me the time to think about what i did. two , it proves how much i care about my friendship with joey. and three , it hurts!", "answer": "  oh hey! hey uh, you remember the necklace i gave you last year? can i see it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": "  why?", "answer": " i just wanna check something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": "   now, we\u0092ll see.", "answer": " air hole! air hole!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": "  here it is! i love it. i wear it all the time.", "answer": "  the necklace i got you was gold, this one is silver.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " huh, well maybe it uh, it changed.", "answer": " oh my god! you actually exchanged it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " well isn\u0092t it better that i exchanged it for something that i enjoy and that i can get a lot of use out of?", "answer": " what did you get?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": "  i\u0092ll get it! i\u0092ll get it! i\u0092ll get it! i\u0092ll get it! i\u0092ll get it! i\u0092ll get it! i\u0092ll get it! i\u0092ll get it! i\u0092ll get it! i\u0092ll get it! i\u0092ll get it! i\u0092ll get it! i\u0092ll get it! i\u0092ll get it!  hi, tim.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " thank you. come meet my friends. this is uh, phoebe.", "answer": " hi, nice to meet you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " and joey.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " hi, joey.", "answer": " my brother, ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " and rachel.  and that\u0092s chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " how do ya do.", "answer": " what\u0092s\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " umm, well, he\u0092s\u009a", "answer": " he\u0092s doin\u0092 some thinkin\u0092!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " what happened? what happened?!", "answer": " you kissed my girlfriend!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " ooh, i like those sunglasses.", "answer": " like \u0091em, like \u0091em? or, i\u0092d like to get store credit for that amount like \u0091em?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " all right everybody, this turkey is ready!", "answer": " where can i wash up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " here, let me show you. okay, the towels are hanging next to the sink, and umm, you can use the fancy soap.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " fancy soap? i thought we were savin\u0092 that for the pope!", "answer": " see he\u0092s nice. right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " yeah, but monica, do you actually want to be in a relationship where you can actually use the phrase, \"that\u0092s not how your dad used to do it.\"", "answer": " wow! everything looks great! where should i sit?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " that doesn\u0092t sound like thinking to me!", "answer": " sorry!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " y\u0092know i don\u0092t think you should be talking at all in there! i think you\u0092ve got to much thinking to do to be talking and making jokes!", "answer": " okay, okay, you got it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " ross, can you pass me the yams?", "answer": " sure! oh, and joey\u0092s got the mashed potatoes if you want to exchange them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " would you stop?! what is the matter with you?!", "answer": " oh-ho-ho, we\u0092ve got company.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " there\u0092s nothing the matter with me. see, i\u0092m not completely devoid of sentiment, see i have feelings.", "answer": " okay, fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " you can\u0092t tell, but i\u0092m trying to break the tension by mooning you guys!", "answer": " all right, look! if this is just a big joke to you, then forget about it, all right?! this means something to me! and if it doesn\u0092t mean anything to you, then you should get out of there, otherwise you\u0092re just an idiot in a box!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " you\u0092re right, and i\u0092m sorry! this means a lot to me! i want you to be my friend again! i swear, i won\u0092t say another word tonight.", "answer": " so are you gonna start taking this thing seriously?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " absolutely!", "answer": " that sounds like another word to me! are you gonna take this seriously?  okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " don\u0092t say that i have no sentiment!  this is a movie stub from our first date! this is an eggshell from the first time you made me breakfast in bed!  this is from the museum from the first time we\u009a were together. okay, maybe i exchange gifts sometimes, but i keep the things that matter!", "answer": " i don\u0092t know what to say, i\u0092m sorry. though, you\u0092re not supposed to take these.  it\u0092s like a million years old, we, we actually, we had people looking for that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " you-you have a very beautiful\u009a eye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " y\u0092know all my friends think this is weird.", "answer": " y\u0092know i-i thought it was gonna be weird, i mean i almost called and canceled, but it really isn\u0092t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " i know! i mean it\u0092s like me and your dad, that\u0092s a totally separate thing.", "answer": " oh, i totally agree.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " nothing. nothing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " no-no really, was-was that not okay?", "answer": " no-no-no that was good, it was, that was uh, that was a goood kiss\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " oh my god! it didn\u0092t remind you of\u009a", "answer": "  don\u0092t say it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " no, but it did! didn\u0092t it?!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " oh man!!", "answer": " i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": "  oh.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " hey. listen, i want you to know how sorry i am\u009a", "answer": " that\u0092s okay. chandler\u0092s the one i\u0092m mad at.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " well, i\u0092m still sorry. is he here?", "answer": " in the box.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": "  chandler?", "answer": " oh, he-he can\u0092t talk right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " why not? what\u0092s going on?", "answer": " he\u0092s just trying to show joey how much he means to him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " by being in a box?", "answer": " joey, had reasons.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " they were threefold.", "answer": " oh. well uh,  you not being able to talk may make this easier. listen umm\u009a  listen i don\u0092t wanna be someone who comes between two best friends. i just, i can\u0092t stand seeing what this is doing to you guys, and i don\u0092t wanna be the cause of that. so, i don\u0092t think we can see each other anymore. i\u0092m gonna go to my mom\u0092s in chicago, i\u0092m gonna stay there for awhile. i think this could\u0092ve be something really amazing, but y\u0092know this is probably for the best. y\u0092know? i\u0092m gonna miss you. good-bye, chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " he can still catch her! come on, get out of there!  get out of there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " so?", "answer": " yeah, we\u0092re gonna be fine! get out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " yeah, you did some real good thinkin\u0092 in there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " oh, he sees her!", "answer": " oh, he\u0092s catching up to her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " oh, she sees him! oh, they\u0092re hugging!", "answer": " he\u0092s taking her purse!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " uhh, that\u0092s not them. i\u0092m gonna go call the police.", "answer": " oh, there they are!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}]